cloud-iq.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy | Cloud IQ

Cloud.IQ Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy explains**  
Cloud.IQ Limited (" **we/us/our** ") is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and we are the owner and operator of [www.cloud-iq.com](https://www.cloud-iq.com/) (the " **Site** "), the our Cloud.IQ product services platform (the " **Platform** ") (together the " **Services** ").

This Privacy Policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us when using the Services. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting the Site and logging-in to and using the Platform, you confirm that you have read and understood the practices described in this Policy.

**Who this Policy applies to**

This Policy applies to:

  * visitors to our Site; 
  * users of our Platform; and
  * job applicants for vacancies at Cloud.IQ Limited.

**Your rights to object**

You have various rights in respect of our use of your personal data as set out in the "Your rights" section below. The fundamental right to be aware of is that you may ask us to consider any valid objections which you have to our use of your personal data where we process your personal data on the basis of our, or another person's, legitimate interest.

We explain in this Policy:

  * Who we are
  * Children
  * Personal data that we collect about you when using the Services and how we use it
  * Our legal basis for use of your personal data
  * Personal data that we share
  * Cookies
  * Security
  * Data retention
  * Your rights
  * Third party sites
  * Changes
  * Contact, complaints, questions and suggestions

**Who we are**

Cloud.IQ Limited is a company registered in England and Wales (registration number 07774309), whose registered office is at Rocketspace, 40-42 Islington High Street, London, N1 8EQ and we are the data controller of the personal data that we collect from you.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about any aspect of our Policy, please contact us using the details set out in the "Contact, complaints, questions and suggestions" section at the end of this Policy.

**Children**

We do not and will not knowingly collect personal data from any unsupervised child under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you may not use the Site unless your parent or guardian has provided us with their consent for your use of this Site.

**Personal data that we collect about you when using the Services and how we use it**

**Visitors to our Site**

What personal data we collect about you | How we use your personal data  
---|---  
  
We, or third parties on our behalf, will collect and use the following personal data about you:

  * your name (first and last);
  * your phone and email details;
  * your city;
  * your country (of business);
  * your company name and website URL;
  * your job role;
  * anything discussed with a chat agent;
  * any comments you make in a blog we post on the Site;
  * the following personal data is created and recorded automatically when you visit our Site:
  * your IP address; and
  * your location (latitude and longitude).

| 

We will collect, use and store your personal data for the following reasons:

  * so that we can administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * improve our Site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * as part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure;
  * measure or understand the effectiveness of messaging we serve to you and others and to make it more relevant;
  * respond to your queries and requests;
  * communicate with you;
  * when you contact us, we may keep a record of your communication to help resolve any issues that you might be facing. We will use your email address to inform you about our Site or products, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements;
  * provide updates to you about any changes to our policies, terms and conditions and any other matters which we may need to tell you; and
  * to contact you via email with marketing to tell you about our products and services.

**Users of our Platform**

What personal data we collect about you | How we use your personal data  
---|---  
  
We, or third parties on our behalf, will collect and use the following personal data about you:

  * your name (first and last);
  * your phone and email details;  

  * your city;  

  * your country (of business);   

  * your company name and website URL;   

  * your job role;   

  * your time zone;
  * the following personal data is created and recorded automatically when you login to and use our Platform: 
    * your IP address; and 
    * your user agent.

| 

We will collect, use and store your personal data for the following reasons:

  * so that we can administer our Platform and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * improve our Platform to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
  * as part of our efforts to keep our Platform safe and secure;
  * measure or understand the effectiveness of messaging we serve to you and others and to make it more relevant;
  * respond to your queries and requests;
  * communicate with you;
  * when you contact us, we may keep a record of your communication to help resolve any issues that you might be facing. We will use your email address to inform you about our Platform or products, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements;
  * provide updates to you about any changes to our policies, terms and conditions and any other matters which we may need to tell you; and
  * to enable us to comply with our obligations under the Licence Agreement we have in place with merchants (your employer) and provide services and support via our Platform.

**Job applicants for vacancies at Cloud.IQ Limited**

What personal data we collect about you | How we use your personal data  
---|---  
  
When you submit an application for an advertised vacancy on the careers page of our  Site, we, or third parties on our behalf, will collect and use the following personal data about you:

  * your name (first and last);
  * your address (optional);
  * your phone and email details;
  * your gender;
  * your LinkedIn details (optional); and
  * information provided in your CV/resume and cover letter.

| 

We, or third parties on our behalf, will collect, use and store your personal data for the following reasons:

  * to process your application (including candidate profiling and suitability assessment);
  * to confirm information on resumes, CVs and covering letters, providing reference letters and performance reference checks;
  * for equal opportunities monitoring;
  * for security vetting, criminal records checks;
  * to comply with any procedures, laws and regulations which apply to us;
  * to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights; and
  * otherwise, for the lawful operation of our business

**Our legal basis for use of your personal data**  
We consider that the legal bases for using your personal data as set out in this Privacy Policy are as follows:

a) our use of your personal data is necessary to perform our obligations under any contract with you (for example, to comply with our obligations under the Licence Agreement we have in place with merchants (your employer) and provide services and support via our Platform); or  
b) our use of your personal data is necessary for complying with our legal obligations (for example, if you contact us requesting access to personal data we hold about you); or   
c) where neither (a) nor (b) apply, use of your personal data is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of others (for example, to ensure the security of our Services). Our legitimate interests are to:

  * run, grow and develop our business;
  * operate our Services;
  * marketing, market research and business development;
  * provide efficient and effective services and products to our merchants; and
  * for internal group administrative purposes

If we rely on our (or another person's) legitimate interests for using your personal data, we will undertake a balancing test to ensure that our (or the other person's) legitimate interests are not outweighed by your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms which require protection of the personal data. You can ask us for information on this balancing test by using the contact details in the "Contact, complaints, questions and suggestions" section below. 

**Personal data that we share**

Most importantly, we never sell your personal data to anyone and only share it as outlined in this Privacy Policy or when you ask us to. We disclose your personal data under the following circumstances:

  * **Group companies** : we will share your personal data with our group companies (including those based outside of the EEA) where it is in our legitimate interests to do so for internal administrative purposes (for example, ensuring consistent and coherent delivery of our services to our merchants, corporate strategy, compliance, auditing and monitoring, research and development and quality assurance). For further information on data sharing outside the EEA, please see the "Where we store your personal data" section below.
  * **Third-party service providers** : we will only share your personal data with third-party service providers to the extent it is necessary for the performance of any contract we enter into with them. This will include: 
    * [**Bugsnag**](https://docs.bugsnag.com/legal/privacy-policy/), who help us to improve the software quality (including capturing errors and diagnostic data) of our Services.
    * [**FullStory**](https://www.fullstory.com/legal/privacy/), who help us improve your user experience as you use our Services.
    * **[Zendesk](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/)**[](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/), who provide a platform to help us improve our user service and engagement with you when using our Services.
    * [**Salesforce**](https://www.salesforce.com/uk/company/privacy/), is our customer relationship management system where we house data on existing and prospective clients.
    * [**Google Analytics**](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3379636?hl=en), who provide analytics services that helps track and report traffic to our Services.
    * [**Snap Engage**](https://snapengage.com/privacy-policy/), who help increase the functionality of our Services and connect us with other third party suppliers we have listed here.
    * [**Hubspot**](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy), who provide software to us which helps us grow and develop deeper relationships with you when you use our Services.
    * [**Google Cloud**](https://policies.google.com/privacy), who are a cloud services provider and host your personal data.
    * [**BambooHR**](https://www.bamboohr.com/privacy.php), who host our job applications page on our Site and collect and process job applicant personal data on our behalf.
  * **Merger or acquisition** : in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets. Alternatively, if Cloud.IQ Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.visitors to our Site; 
  * **Compliance with laws and legal proceedings** : we will share information with companies, organisations or individuals outside Cloud.IQ Limited if we believe that disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to meet any law, regulation, or governmental order.
  * **Third party investigators, authorities or law enforcement bodies** : if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to enforce or apply our Terms and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Cloud.IQ Limited our customers, or others.
  * **Third party training services** : if we agree to share your details as part of a partnership agreement to offer content and training services.

**Where we store your personal data**

Your personal data will be used, stored and/or accessed by staff operating outside of the EEA working for us, other members of our group, or third party suppliers, including those located in the United States of America and Australia. Further details on to whom your personal data may be disclosed are set out in the "Personal data that we share" section.

When we provide any personal data about you to any such non-EEA based members of our group or third party suppliers, we will take appropriate measures to ensure that the recipient protects your personal data adequately. These measures may include the following permitted in Articles 45 and 46 of the General Data Protection Regulation:

a) in the case of US-based entities, entering into European Commission approved standard contractual arrangements with them, or ensuring they have signed up to the EU-US Privacy Shield (see further https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome); or  
b) in the case of entities based in other countries outside the EEA (including Australia), entering into European Commission approved standard contractual arrangements with them.

Further details on the steps we take to protect your personal data in these cases is available from us on request by contacting us using the details set out in the "Contact, complaints, questions and suggestions" section at the end of this Policy.

**Cookies**  

Some pages on our Services use cookies, which are small files placed on your internet browser when you visit and use our Services. We use cookies in order to offer you a more tailored experience in the future, by understanding and remembering your particular browsing preferences.

Where we use cookies on our Services, you may block these at any time. To do so, you can activate the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies), you may not be able to access all or parts of our Services or to use all the functionality provided through our Services.

Read our [Cookie Policy](https://www.cloud-iq.com/cookie-policy) to learn more about the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them.

**Security**

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard the personal data that you provide to us unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Services. 

**Data Retention**

We keep your personal data for no longer than necessary for the purposes for which the personal data is processed. The length of time for which we retain personal data depends on the purposes for which we collect and use it and/or as required to comply with applicable laws and to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

If you are an unsuccessful job applicant, we keep your personal data for 1 year after the conclusion of the job application process, unless we are required by law to keep your personal data for longer or delete it sooner.

**Your rights**

You have certain rights in relation to your personal data. If you would like further information in relation to these or would like to exercise them, please contact us at support@cloud-iq.com at any time. You have the right to request that we:

  * provide access to any personal data we hold about you;
  * update any of your personal data which is out of date or incorrect;
  * delete any personal data which we are holding about you;
  * restrict the way that we process your personal data;
  * provide your personal data to a third party provider of services;
  * provide you with a copy of any personal data which we hold about you; or
  * consider any valid objections which you have to our use of your personal data.

We will consider all such requests and provide our response within a reasonable period (and in any event within any time period required by applicable law). Please note, however, that certain personal data may be exempt from such requests in certain circumstances.

If an exception applies, we will tell you this when responding to your request. We may request you provide us with information necessary to confirm your identity before responding to any request you make.

**Third party sites**

Our Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**Changes**

This Policy was last updated on 29/05/2018.

Any changes we may make to our Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where we make significant changes to this Policy, we will post a pop-up on our Services notifying you of the changes, or if we have your email address, we will email you notifying you of the changes. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Policy.

**Contact, complaints, questions and suggestions**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Policy are welcomed and please contact us:

By post: Cloud.IQ Limited, Rocketspace, 40-42 Islington High Street, London, N1 8EQ  
By email: [support@cloud-iq.com](mailto:support@cloud-iq.com)

If you have a complaint about how we use your personal data, we would always prefer you to contact us first. However, you may also make a complaint to the data protection regulator in the country where you usually live or work, or where an alleged infringement of the General Data Protection Regulation has taken place. Alternatively, you may seek a remedy through the courts if you believe your rights have been breached. For the UK, the supervisory authority is the Information Commissioner's Office, details of which can be found [here](https://ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint/).
